Loot Welcome to Rupees Like Share and
Subscribe Protest against looting of traders
and you people have given details of Meghvadh Bank
whose numbers will be known tomorrow but we will give the numbers and to
tell that in the morning present in the studio
from home Securities weak
ICICI Lombard weak Papa will do it
now some creation has been done by our
family Bodh Bhikshu weakness is
seen coming the market is believing two types
of things on one hand it is believing which is
in the reports that the
bank posts the numbers on its website but many people
who come on this side of Bhanwarlal Meghwal
mix, it is a
rough estimate
that you can see here that this can also be added
which is estimated to be upwards of 3537 4000 crores,
quality on a little site
soon, if we talk about the 27th number in the market regarding midnight, then
these were 12621 crores, the
figure can post a comeback in this quarter
from 10,000 in front of Chhattisgarh,
apart from this, approximately sequence
of growth of around three and a quarter percent on the low base of
that  A rise of around 21%
can be seen here on one number.
On the profit front, 6600 to 29 thousand 630 crores will be standing.
You will see this 7% impact in front of the 449 court, but
what impact will this 7% have on the sequence also,
from both the perspectives, the numbers are
expected to be posted on this site.
From this table, the quality will be stable and I am and
sometimes it will
remain in this skirt situated between 3000 to 4000 crores, but there
is commentary part and question and because the
higher levels have become quite soft, then
maybe if the market town surprises everyone, then
it can be a good statue, but the
surprise element is very important,
after that something will happen, well, it is a good thing that there will be a
holiday, we will understand this
and will react on Monday, the second time
Infosys also did the same, we have now become
scientific, it is
difficult but from this,
looking at the model number from Bank of India, ICC Bank behavior update, Chure Bank and
HDFC  The bank has to be
switched on,
do both of these,
if one has to do only these two then
I think that
both the transactions of SDMC will be in the right category, one
should invest in ICC Bank, but
if one has to exit somewhere else then I
think Kotak Kewal Missions has become
much better after so many corrections and as far as the
question is about the reaction to the results of AC, then
Sumit told in blunt words
what happened with Infosys, so at this time
if one wants to play only on the results then
I think one should fold it once, we will
see on Monday how it will be, but